本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
闯进拥挤的走廊
<i>Crashing through the crowded halls</i>
躲过蜂拥的女孩
<i>Dodging girls like Ping-Pong balls</i>
只为及时赶到洗手间
<i>Just to reach the bathroom on time</i>
欢迎关注迪幻微博 @迪幻Deefun
迪幻微信公众号 ideefun
脏衣服堆成山
<i>Leaping over laundry piles</i>
臭尿布闻不完
<i>Diapers you can smell for miles</i>
■
时间轴： 陵醯   Coover
拼尽全力才能求生存
<i>Guy's got to do what he can to survive</i>
喧闹的一家  喧闹的一家
<i>In the Loud house, in the Loud house</i>
■
翻译： 绿豆布丁   Mirro   JlilaCY   乔乔央央
追跑闪躲  推搡打闹
<i>Duck, dodge, push, and shove</i>
是我们对爱的宣告
<i>Is how we show our love</i>
喧闹的一家  喧闹的一家
<i>In the Loud house, in the Loud house</i>
■
校订： PPMilkovich   板栗
一个男孩  十个姐妹
<i>One boy and ten girls</i>
世界给我都不换
<i>Wouldn't trade it for the world</i>
■
后期： 黑潘
喧闹  喧闹  喧闹
<i> Loud Loud Loud</i>
喧闹一家亲
<i>Loud house</i>
喧闹一家亲  第三季第三集
The Loud House  S03E03  White Hare/Insta-Gran
第一段标题
你可能很好奇
You may be wondering,
究竟谁才是劳德一家中最酷炫的人
"Who's the cool new guy in the Loud house?"
那就是我  林肯
It's me, Lincoln!
我实在等不及和你们分享我改变造型的原因了
And I can't wait to tell you why I've changed my look.
-是这样的  -林肯
- See-- - Lincoln!
你准备好
Are you ready to
和那个新搬来的女孩搭讪了吗
introduce yourself to the new girl today?
或者让克莱德来告诉你们原因吧
Or Clyde can tell you.
那当然了
That's an affirmative.
一切准备就绪
I'm all set.
我扯了新线头
Got my new threads...
贴了临时纹身
A temporary tat...
准备了一大串从一本青年杂志里
and a list of hip slang that I picked up
收集来的流行语
from a teen magazine.
太棒了  老兄
That's great, buddy,
但是你真的需要这么多准备吗
but do you really need all that?
你已经很酷炫了
You're already cool.
你那天甚至骑着车从水坑上跳过去
You jumped that puddle on your bike the other day.
这个嘛  根据她的穿着和她头上戴的蝴蝶结来看
Well, from the way she wears that bow in her hair,
这个新来的女生肯定酷毙了  我决不能输给她
the new girl seems super cool, so I gotta up my game.
我理解
I hear you.
而且你只有一次机会
And you only get one chance
给别人留下好的第一印象
to make a good first impression.
如果你搞砸了  就要等到
If you blow this, you'll have to wait for
下一个女生搬到镇上了
another girl to move to town,
那要等到猴年马月啊
and who knows when that'll be?
谢谢你给我的额外压力
Thank you for that added pressure.
不用谢
Don't mention it.
那么  你的计划是什么
So, what's the plan?
今天早上我会在校车上制造和她的偶遇
I'm gonna catch her on the bus this morning
这样我们就有一对一的交流时间了
so I can have some one-on-one time with her.
不错  你需要帮手吗
Good thinking. You need a wingman?
谢了  不过作为男人有些事要一个人上
Thanks, but there are some things a man must do alone.
明白了
I get that.
我第一次上公共卫生间的时候
I said the same thing to my dads
也和我爸说过一样的话
the first time I used a public restroom.
祝你好运  哥们
Good luck, buddy.
现在我只剩下最后一道障碍了
And now I have just one last obstacle:
在我的姐妹弄清楚我想干什么前
to get out of the house before my sisters
溜出家门
figure out what I'm up to.
慢着
Hold it!
嘿
Heeey!
早上好  女士们
Mornin', ladies.
难道你不知道
Did you really think we wouldn't notice
你穿的就像个无比典型的
that you're dressed like a stereotypical
五十年代好莱坞润滑工吗
Hollywood representation of a 1950s greaser?
这是凝胶  又不是润滑物
This is gel, not grease.
再说了  一个男人就不能
And besides, can't a guy wear
换一种穿衣风格去上学吗
something different to school for a change?
-在咱们家就不行  -现在  告诉我们你在隐瞒什么
- Not in this house. - Now, what's the sitch, bro?
我什么都没有隐瞒
There is no sitch!
林肯  快接
Lincoln, come in!
我想到了一些你能和那个新来的女孩
I thought of some topics for you to discuss
搭讪的话题
with the new girl.
新来的女孩
New girl?
就像玉米坚果
Like corn nuts.
它们到底是玉米呢  还是坚果呢
Are they corn, or are they nuts? Discuss.
现在没空  克莱德
Not now, Clyde.
我待会儿给你回电话
I gotta call you back.
所以你觉得穿这身能吸引那个新来的姑娘
So you thought you'd impress the new girl by wearing this?
不  不  不
No. No, no, no.
我不需要你们的帮忙
I don't need your help.
我早就计划好了
I've got it all planned out.
-林肯  -不要
- Lincoln? - No!
我敢肯定你们有你们自己的方案
I'm sure you have your own plan
还想说服我该怎么做
and want to tell me what to do,
上次我接受了你们的建议
but the last time I took your girl advice,
结果我糗大了
I ended up with a black eye.
-但是林肯  -不
- But Lincoln-- - No.
我只有一次机会
I've only got one chance
给别人留下好的第一印象
to make a good first impression,
我想自己来处理
and I want to do it my way.
-林肯  -看  免费披萨
- Lincoln! - Look! Free pizza!
希望夹克没染上汗臭
Whew. Hope I didn't stink up the jacket.
校车来之前我就躲在这儿吧
I'll hide here until the bus comes.
嘿  过来  小家伙
Hey, there, little guy.
二十三  二十四  二十五
Twenty-three, twenty-four, twenty-five?
老天  你的姐妹可真多啊
Man, that's a lot of sisters.
我简直无法想象那样的生活
I can't even imagine what that would be like.
喂  林肯
Hey, Lincoln!
慢着
Hold it!
嘿
Heeey!
早上好  女士们
Mornin', ladies.
你为什么穿得像个
Why are you dressed like a hoodlum
来自外星的流氓
from the wrong side of the forest?
没错  你在隐瞒什么
Yeah! What's the sitch?
我什么也没有隐瞒
There is no sitch.
沃伦  快接  我是丹尼
Warren, come in. It's Danny.
我想到了一些你可以和新来的女孩
I thought of some topics for you to discuss
搭讪的话题
with the new girl.
新来的女孩
New girl?
就像  黄油生菜
Like this. Butter lettuce.
到底是黄油呢  还是生菜呢
Is it butter, or is it lettuce? Discuss.
丹尼  我待会儿给你回电话
Danny, I'll call you back.
快和我们说说她的底细
Tell us everything about her.
没什么可说的  贝蒂
There's nothing to tell, Betty.
只是学校里新来的一个女同学
It's just a new girl at school.
我已经开始讨厌她了
I hate her already.
你还不认识她呢  布兰达
You don't even know her, Brenda.
你不也是  所以我们才要帮助你
Neither do you. That's why we're helping.
哦  我超爱帮人撮合的
Ooh! I love matchmaking.
有什么用呢
What's the use?
生命只是一段偶有绝望点缀的
Life's just an endless stretch of misery,
漫长而痛苦的经历
occasionally brightened by despair.
我觉得你身上的轮穴需要重新组合  贝拉
I think your chakras need some, like, realignment, Bella.
快看  各位  我用油画记录下了这个瞬间
Look, guys, I've captured the moment in oils.
题目叫做
I call it "Portrait of a Clueless Boy
亲姐妹们拯救无知的少年
Being Saved by His Sisters."
你们听着  我不需要你们的帮助
Guys! I don't need your help.
是的  你需要
"Yes, you do"?
不  我不需要  布丽姬
No, I don't, Bridget!
是的  你需要
Yes, you do.
根据我的测算  你成功搞定
By my calculations, the chances of you
新来的女孩的概率
successfully courting said new girl
只有可怜的25分之1
without our help are an abysmal 25 to 1.
是啊  我都习惯这种几率了
Yeah. I'm quite used to those odds.
要是你的计划失效了呢
Well, what if your plan doesn't work?
要是它毁了你唯一一个
What if you ruin your only chance
给她留下好的第一印象的机会呢
to make a good first impression?
要是你因此而孤独终老呢
What if you grow old and alone?
要是我也也孤独终老了呢
What if I grow old and alone?
要是世界末日就是明天呢
What if the world ends tomorrow?
-要是  -姐妹们
- What if-- - Guys.
我要没时间了
I'm running out of time.
现在请允许我先走一步
Now, if you'll excuse me, I'm leaving.
是吗  老弟
Oh, yeah, mate?
那你要怎么对付我们二十五个人呢
And just 'ow do you plan on gettin' past the 25 of us?
这个  我打算
Well, I plan to...
跑
ruuun!
抓住他
Get him!
这时候要来点刺激的音乐
This calls for some chase music!
我没有把这个列在今天的计划表里
I didn't have this on my to-do list for the day,
管他的呢
but what the heck?
沃伦  你给我站住
Warren, you stop running this instant,
不然我就去告诉妈妈
or I'm telling Mom!
看  那亮晶晶的是什么
Look! Shiny object!
哦  在哪儿  啥
Ooh! Where? Huh?
抓住他  贝丝
Grab him, Beth!
贝丝
Beth!
啥  怎么了
Huh? What?
贝丝  快行动起来
Ugh! Beth! Get in the game!
加油
Go...
字幕
Rope them doggies!
-抓住了  -把我放下  贝莎
- Gotcha. - Put me down, Bertha!
这剧情刺激得我的毛也跟着立起来了呢
What a hare-raising development!
懂没
Get it?
沃伦  亲爱的
Oh, Warren, honey,
你全都做错了
you're going about this all wrong.
-全错  -对
- Totes. - Yeah!
把那些东西还给我
Give me those back!
我得打扮的酷一点
I need to look cool.
得了吧  女孩子不喜欢装酷的
Please. Girls don't want a cool guy.
女孩子真正喜欢的是感性的男孩子
Warren, what girls really want is a sensitive guy.
把皮衣扔了  换这件淡紫色的衣服
Ditch the leather and go with lavender.
淡紫色和你的毛发更配哦
It's a much better match for your fur tones.
念诗给她听
Read her a poem.
和她共享一杯健康又好喝的海藻思慕雪
Offer to share a healthy and delicious kelp smoothie.
但别忘了先问问她会不会过敏
But check her allergies first.
带上这根幸运兔脚
Take this rabbit's foot for luck.
赞美她的衣着
Compliment her clothes.
-还有她的眼睛  -可是
- Compliment her eyes. - But
-要善良  -可是
- Be kind. - But
-要浪漫  -可是
- Be romantic. - But
-要展示你自己
- Be present.
-可是  -好了  去吧
- But - Now, go!
你是刚搬来皇林区的吧
You're new to Royal Woods, aren't you?
我都观察你好几天了
I've been watching you for days.
什么
Uh, what?
我是说  我想自我介绍一下
I-I mean, I've been meaning to introduce myself.
我叫沃伦
I'm Warren.
非常高兴认识你  沃伦
Oh. Nice to meet you, Warren.
我喜欢你的大耳朵
I like how big your ears are.
-我的耳朵很大吗  -不  不
- They're big? - No! No.
你也会越长越大的
Uh, you'll grow into them.
对了  你喜欢诗吗
I mean, do you like poems?
“我能将你比作暖暖夏日吗”
"Shall I compare thee to a summer's day?
“但你比屁可爱”  我是说  “比它”
Thou fart more lovely--" I-I mean, "Thou art more."
你喜欢黄油生菜吗
What do you think about butter lettuce?
我刚想起来  我忘记带背包了
You know, I just remembered, I forgot my backpack.
等等  你想不想尝尝海藻思慕雪
Wait! Want to share a kelp smoothie?
好吧  当然了
Um, sure. Why not?
太好了  不对  等等
Great! Oh, wait.
在你喝之前我还要问一句
Before you drink any,
你不过敏吧
do you have any allergies?
因为我不想看见你长出那种
'Cause I'd hate to see you break out
全是脓的大水疱
in pus-filled blisters.
我改主意了  还是不喝了
Ew! On second thought, no, thanks.
真的吗  很好喝的哎
Are you sure? It's really delicious.
呸  跟肥料一个味
Blegh! It tastes like manure.
真抱歉  我倒是带着手帕呢
Sorry. I'm sure I have a hankie.
哎呦不对  拿错了
Oh, whoops. That's not it.
那是根  兔子脚吗
Ew! Is that a rabbit's foot?
什么  不是  只是根长毛的奶酪棒
What? No! Just a fuzzy mozzarella stick.
真抱歉  我来帮你擦
Sorry. Let me help you.
虽然你的衣服上也脏了  不过不要紧
Uh, that stain ought to come out just fine.
这样你就又能买件新裙子了
If not, you'll have an excuse to get a new dress.
反正橙色也和你的毛色不搭
Orange totally clashes with your fur tones anyways.
-什么  -这个怪咖惹到你了吗
- What? - Is this creep bothering you?
对
Yes.
你个穿紫衬衫的
Hey. Lavender shirt.
你知不知道让女孩生气是很不酷的啊
Don't you know it ain't cool to upset a lady?
-但我只是想  -滚开
- But I was just-- - Take a hike.
来吧
Come on.
咱们离开这里
Let's get out of here.
我喜欢你的皮夹克
I like your leather jacket.
你好酷啊
You're so cool.
一切还都顺利吗
So... how'd it go?
我不怎么想说
I don't want to talk about it.
你也不用说了
Ah, you don't have to.
我刚才在灌木丛里暗中观察到了一切
I watched the whole thing from the bushes.
我那么努力的想给人留个好印象
So much for making a good first impression.
没事的  伙计
It's okay, pal.
我相信很快又会有新兔子搬来皇林区的
I'm sure a new bunny will move to the woods soon...
只要这里的狼口比例能下降
well, once our coyote population goes down.
我不明白为什么你突然改变了计划
I don't understand why you changed your plan.
你为什么要穿成那样
Why did you dress like that and say those things
说那些话  还做马便便味的思慕雪呢
and make horse poop smoothies?
相信我  我没想改变计划
Believe me, I didn't want to change my plan.
但是我的姐妹们来了
But then my sisters came along,
你知道她们的
and, well, you know how they are.
我知道贝蒂
I know how Betty is.
你不会又在想象她跳灌木丛
Are you picturing her hopping through the woods
的慢动作镜头吧
in slo-mo again?
什么  怎么会
Whaaat? No.
瞧你干的好事
A lot of good you did me.
真是噩梦啊
Wow. What a nightmare.
看来逃离我的姐妹们是绝对正确的选择
I was definitely right to run away from my sisters.
她们会毁了这一切的
They would've ruined everything.
别听她们的  她们会坏事的
Don't listen to them! They'll ruin everything!
她们不知道自己在干什么
They don't know what they're doing.
说不定她们知道自己在干什么
Whoa. Maybe they do know what they're doing.
也就是说
Which means maybe
我的姐妹们也知道自己在干什么
my sisters know what they're doing.
也就是说  她们的计划可能比我的好
Which means maybe their plan's better than mine.
也就是说  我不该再继续自言自语了
Which means maybe I should stop talking to myself
因为还剩五分钟
because I only have five minutes to find them
公交车就要来了
before the bus arrives!
哦不  我来迟了
Oh, no! I'm too late!
他们走了
They're gone.
我错过了多好的机会啊
Ah! I'm gonna miss my big chance!
太好了  你们还没走
Oh, thank goodness you haven't left yet.
我知道我错了  我需要你们的帮助
Look, I was wrong. I want your help.
我的计划会失败的
My plan is going to fail.
快告诉我你们的计划
Tell me your plan.
-告诉我该做什么  -林肯
- Tell me what to do! - Lincoln
-告诉我该穿什么  -林肯
- Tell me what to wear. - Lincoln
-告诉我该怎么做  -林肯
- Tell me how to act! - Lincoln!
-告诉我该说什么  -林肯
- Tell me what to say! - Lincoln!
什么
What?
我们不会告诉你那些事的
We weren't going to tell you any of those things.
什么  为什么  你们不是想改造我吗
What? Why? You didn't want to change me?
不  我们想知道你为什么要改造自己
No. We wanted to know why you changed yourself.
我只是
I just...
我只是觉得
I just thought...
林肯  现在的你就很完美了
Lincoln, you're perfect just the way you are.
-你很善良  -你很时尚
- You're kind. - You're fashionable.
-你很摇滚  -你很幽默
- You're rockin'. - You're funny.
-你很坚强  -你很有深度
- You're tough. - You're deep.
-你很友善  -你很聪明
- You're friendly. - You're smart.
你四林肯·劳德
You Yincoln Youd.
给我那件夹克
Now, give me that jacket.
然后出门  好好做自己
And go out there, and just be you.
我还能赶上
Ah! I can still make it.
等等
Wait!
-你差点没赶上  -刚刚好
- You almost missed it! - Just made it.
嗨  我叫林肯·劳德
Hello. Um, my, uh, name is Lincoln Loud.
很高兴认识你  林肯·劳德
Nice to meet you, Lincoln Loud.
你是新搬来皇林区住的吗
So, you're new to Royal Woods?
对啊  做新来的小孩挺孤独的
Yeah, it's lonely being the new kid in town.
可能你还没有遇到合适的人
Maybe you just haven't met the right people yet.
你想坐这里吗吗
Would you like to sit down?
我还以为你要赶不上这趟车了
Um, I didn't think you were gonna catch the bus.
是啊  幸好我穿的像个路标一样
Yeah. Good thing I'm dressed like a caution cone,
不然司机可能就看不到我了
or the driver never would've seen me.
你真幽默  林肯·劳德
You're funny, Lincoln Loud.
吃胡萝卜条吗
Carrot stick?
谢啦
Thanks.
对了  那你叫什么啊
Oh, by the way, what's your name?
第二段标题
他们来了
They're here!
今晚对劳德家来说可是非常重要的
It's a big night at the Loud house.
爷爷要来吃晚饭
Pop Pop's coming to dinner,
而且他会带一位特殊的客人
and he's bringing a very special guest.
我的家人们
Hey, family!
我给大家介绍一下这位对我很重要的人  默特尔
I'd like you all to meet my main squeeze, Myrtle.
很高兴见到你  默特尔
Nice to meet you, Myrtle.
我来给你介绍下他们
Let me introduce everyone.
不用了
Oh, no need.
看看我猜的对不对
Let me see if I have this right...
洛丽  兰妮  露娜  卢安  琳恩
Lori, Leni, Luna, Luan, Lynn,
林肯  露西  拉娜
Lincoln, Lucy, Lana,
萝拉  丽萨和莉莉
Lola, Lisa, and Lily.
哇塞  按生日来排的
Wow. In birth order!
真的很了不起
That's impressive.
不啦  更了不起的是你们养了
Well, what's impressive is raising
这些可爱的小孩
such delightful children.
艾伯特  帮我拿外衣可以么
Albert, can you get my coat?
林恩
Oh, Lynn.
你做的食物简直是天国之美
Your food is just heavenly.
谢谢你的夸奖  你的嘴真甜
Oh, you're sweet to say that.
没你的玉米甜
Not as sweet as this corn!
我不能再笑了  我有牙套了
I can't have any 'cause I have braces.
当这个时间见到你的笑容时  最好他们能控制住自己
Well, the world better brace itself for your pretty smile.
林恩二代
Oh, Lynn Jr.
那些是你的奖杯么
Are those your trophies?
爷爷说你拿到六个不同领域的冠军
Pop Pop said you were named MVP on six different teams.
嗯  准确说是七个
Well, technically seven,
他们还不熟桌上冰球
but they don't recognize air hockey yet.
我的爸爸的爸爸有将我的成就
Has my paternal forebearer familiarized you
给你介绍么
with my achievements?
当然了
Oh, you bet.
他告诉我你所有的关于粪便的研究
He told me all about your fecal research.
令人印象深刻
Impressive stuff.
想想看我的幻灯片么
Would you like to see some slides?
吃晚饭再说好么  亲爱的
Maybe after dinner, sweetie.
这是艾斯萨维
So this is Ace Savvy,
和他的伙伴  独眼杰克
and here's his partner, One-Eyed Jack.
纸牌双关语啊  真聪明
Card puns? How clever!
不好意思打扰你们游戏
Sorry to break up the fun,
但是默特尔和我要走了
but Myrtle and I should get going.
不好意思我还没有碰到你的泥巴  拉娜
Oh, I'm sorry I didn't get to sample your mud pies, Lana.
没关系  我给你做了一个在路上玩
It's okay. Made you one for the road.
使用之前别玩了加热
Don't forget to heat before serving.
谢谢今天这一切
Thank you for everything.
能遇见你们真的很开心
Oh, it was so wonderful meeting you all.
再见
Bye!
-晚点见  -早点回来
- See you later! - Come back soon!
真想把你们都带回家
I might just take you up on that.
她是不是很棒
Isn't she great?
还好我把她从西摩那抢过来了
Good thing I stole her away from Seymour.
那只猎狗看中了她
That hound dog had his eye on her.
没错  是他离开了  再见咯
Yeah. His left one. Buh-bye!
-她好棒啊  -我爱她
- She was so nice. - I loved her!
默特尔  等等
Myrtle, wait!
我的粪便幻灯片
My fecal slides!
嗨  家人
Oh, hi, fam!
我找到你们藏起来的钥匙
I found your hide-a-key.
是不是藏在草丛里
Uh, wasn't it under the thornbushes?
还有  我找到你的绷带了
Also, I found your bandages.
我没办法等到你们回来
I just couldn't wait to get back over here
想早点和我十一个孙子孙女相处
and spend some more time with my 11 new grandkids.
说到这里  惊喜
Speaking of which... surprise!
我用我的胶水抢做的
I made these with my glue gun.
“和奶奶在一起生活更开心”
"Life is sweeter with a Gran Gran"?
你用胶水做做这些的时候  有没有注意通风啊
Was your room well ventilated when you worked with this glue?
我想你们都可以叫我奶奶了
I was thinking that maybe you kids could call me Gran Gran.
为什么不试试叫一声呢
Why don't you try 'em on?
嗷  你们真的是太可爱了
Aww! You look so cute.
现在  过来
Now, come on!
我还有更多惊喜
I have even more surprises.
你对我的蜘蛛网干了什么
What have you done with my cobwebs?
亲爱的
Oh, sweetie.
我把它们都打下来了
I tore them all down,
因为里面还有蜘蛛
'cause they had spiders in them.
对啊  伊利亚  玛利亚  还有小乔乔
Yes. Elijah, Amaria, and Little Jojo.
希望他们安息
May they rest in peace.
我的幸运泽西呢
Uh, where are my lucky jerseys?
应该在这里有一块很乱的地方  就在那里
They should be in a big messy pile right here.
我全部拿去干洗了
I took 'em to the dry cleaners.
每一处污渍都干净了
They got every last stain out.
还有那些使我幸运的
So everything that made them lucky.
像你这样的实力选手怎么会需要呢
Well, who needs luck when you have talent like yours?
总而言之  我已经发现
In conclusion, I have identified
重要的同位素能用在
the necessary isotope for--
你在和你的科学家朋友们聊天呢
Ooh! You're talking to your little science friends?
你们好啊  我是丽萨的奶奶
Hi! I'm Lisa's Gran Gran.
嗯  我们在做一件
Yes... we're in the middle
很重要的事情
of something important right now.
你可能需要避让一些
Perhaps you could excuse us.
对嗷  这样吧  你们继续做你们的事
Oh, you know what,you just do your thing
当我不存在就好
like I'm not even here.
我帮你收拾收拾就好了
And I'll just be tidying up.
我建议你不要
I-I prefer you don't!
这些烧杯里都是垃圾
Ooh!These beakers are full of junk!
不要  等等
No! Wait!
我一般都去理发店
I usually have a barber do this...
为什么你有奶奶了还要在陌生人身上花钱呢
Well, why pay a stranger when you've got a Gran Gran?
看  哈  你看起来真的很帅
There! Ah! You look so handsome!
你的发型就像一个碗倒过来
That haircut really bowls me over!
闪亮亮
Spit shine!
看  这样  没泥土  没化妆
Ah, there. No mud. No makeup.
就闪亮亮的脸
Just sparkling faces
沾点牛排酱我就能吃下去了
that I could eat right now with some steak sauce.
我们的“指甲油大战”系列怎么不见了
Um, what happened to our episodes of "Nail Polish Wars"?
我全删了
Oh, I deleted those.
是的  这样的  那些话语太不正能量了
Yeah, see, the language is just so negative.
再见咯  宝宝们
Adios, grandbabies!
会再见的
See you real soon!
那女人简直是噩梦
That woman is a nightmare.
我才不要叫她奶奶
No way I'm calling her Gran Gran.
更糟糕了  看  她留下他的日程表
It gets worse! Look. She left her day planner.
我这个季度所有的比赛
She's coming to all my games
她都回来
for the rest of the season?
我瑞典的研讨会
My conference in Sweden?
她没有一点空闲时间么
How did she get clearance?
我和鲍比的下个约会她也要来
She's coming on my next date with Bobby?
我们必须做点什么
We have to do something.
我们不能这样过下去
We can't live like this!
尤其是你  兄弟
You especially can't, brah.
所以  现在要做一件事
Well... there is one thing we could do.
分开他们
Break them up.
-萝拉  -那太不好了
- Lola! - That's terrible!
真的不好么
Is it, though?
我意思是  爷爷那么好一人
I mean, Pop Pop is such an awesome guy.
真的和默特尔那样的人定下来么
Should he really settle for someone like Myrtle?
她说得对
She has a point.
那  就算我们想做
Well, even if we wanted to do that,
我们要怎么做
how would we?
我有个主意
I might have an idea.
还记得爷爷说的
Remember when Pop Pop said
西摩总是盯着默特尔吗
that Seymour had his eye on Myrtle?
-没错  用他的左眼  -也许这就是办法
- Yeah, the left one. - Maybe that's our answer.
我给爷爷做了一整壶的柠檬汁
I made this whole pitcher of lemonade for my grandpa,
但是他有胃酸返流
but he's got acid reflux.
我该把这个怎么处理呢
Whatever shall I do with it?
噢  给我一杯吧
Ooh! I'll take a glass.
给你  西摩先生
Here you are, Mr. Seymour, sir!
噢  好酸
Ooh! Tart.
我的汤真的太烫了
Oh, my soup's literally too hot!
我该怎么喝啊
How am I ever going to eat it?
我来帮你吧  亲爱的
Oh, let me help, dear.
现在让我们来制造爱的联系
And now to make a love connection.
大功告成
Bingo.
林肯  4点才知道我们能不能成功
Um, Lincoln, Bingo's not till 4:00.
准备行动
Rad job, dude.
爷爷肯定会嫉妒的
That's gonna make Pop Pop way jealous.
我敢保证他们今晚就会分手
I bet he breaks it off with her tonight!
琳恩  该你上了
Okay, Lynn. You're up.
琳恩怎么还没好
Man, what's taking Lynn so long?
任务完成
Mission accomplished.
好了  我们得在别人发现我们之前赶快走
Okay, let's get out of here before anyone sees us.
太晚了
Too late!
我已经发现你们了
I see you!
你们这群小天使
Oh, you angels came
一定是来参加我的生日派对的吧
for my birthday party, didn't you?
-当然  -没错
- Of course! - Of course!
好了  我们到了  派对会场
Well, here we are. Party central.
等你们爷爷来
As soon as your Pop Pop gets here,
我们的派对就可以开始了
we can get this shindig started.
我们不应该再等等其他人吗
Shouldn't we wait for the other guests too?
没有其他人了
Oh, no other guests.
那你的家人呢
What about your family?
我没有别的家人了
Well, I don't really have any.
我是独生女
I was an only child, and somehow,
而且我原来也从没考虑过结婚
I never got around to getting hitched.
我一直都忙于旅行和做我自己的事情
I was just too busy traveling and living my life.
实话说  我原来从没想要有一个家
To be honest, I never really missed having a family,
直到我遇到了你们的爷爷  还有你们
until I met your Pop Pop and you guys,
虽然你们不是我真正的家人
and, well, I know you're not my real family,
但是你们完全给了我家人的感觉
but gosh darn, you all sure feel like it.
默尔特  我们能先失陪一下吗
Um, Myrtle, can you excuse us for a second?
我们需要去一下洗手间
We, um, all have to go to the bathroom.
你们是想去找你们的爷爷吧
You take after your Pop Pop.
洛丽  你想干嘛  我可不需要来洗手间
Okay, what gives, Lori? I don't have to tinkle!
你们还不明白吗
Don't you guys get it?
这就是为什么默尔特总想管我们
This is why Myrtle's been smothering us so much.
她自己没有成家
She never had a family of her own.
大概是想借此来弥补失去的时光吧
She's probably just trying to make up for lost time.
没错  她有时确实太强势了
Yes, she can come on a little strong,
但是她的出发点是好的
but her heart's in the right place.
-我觉得很内疚  -我也是
- I feel terrible. - Me too.
我们应该去道歉
We should go apologize.
可我们现在有一个更大的问题
Uh, guys? We have a bigger problem.
我们已经把照片放在爷爷家门缝里了
We put that photo under Pop Pop's door.
好了  计划有变
Okay. New plan.
拉娜和萝拉  你们去拖住默尔特
Twins, you distract Myrtle.
琳恩和林肯  你们把照片取回来
Lynn and Lincoln, you get the photo back.
我们剩下的人去找爷爷
The rest of us will find Pop Pop
拖住他让他先别回家
and keep him away from his room.
解散
Break!
我们出发吧  林肯
Let's move out, Lincoln.
你什么时候换上的忍者服
Hey, when did you change into your ninja suit?
你的蘑菇头怎么不见了
What happened to your bowl cut?
-问得好  -啊
- Touché. - Hai!
锁上了  这不是问题
Locked. Not a problem.
交给我
I got this.
谢谢你  夫人
Thanks, lady.
哦不  他已经看过了
Oh, no! He's already seen it!
救民啊  来人把这个疯子拖走
Help! Someone call this maniac off!
我早知道你看上了我的女朋友
I knew you had your eye on my girl!
没有
That's not true.
我的左眼不受控制的
The left one's got a mind of its own.
照片可不会说谎  西摩
Pictures don't lie, Seymour.
现在我该找你算账了
And now I'm gonna take it to ya.
你真是个疯子
You're a crazy man!
爷爷住手
Pop Pop, stop!
你们别管
Stay out of this, kids.
这位多情先生自找的麻烦
Mr. Kissy Face has it coming.
完了
Dang it.
爷爷
Pop Pop!
-放开他  -放开他
- Let him go! - Let him go!
-发生了什么  -爷爷
- What is going on? - Pop Pop!
叫苏
Call Sue!
叫所有人出来
Call anybody!
老头打架
Geezer fight!
我赌埃尔伯特赢
I got 50 bucks on Al.
-哈  -爷爷住手
- Ha! - Pop Pop, no!
照片是假的
The photo's fake!
-什么  -他说的没错
- What? - It's true.
我们用电脑合成的照片
We made it on our computer.
你们为什么要这么做
Why in the heck would you do something like that?
说实话  我们本来想让你和默尔特分手的
The truth is, we were trying to break you and Myrtle up.
你们不喜欢默尔特吗
Don't you like Myrtle?
我们之前不理解她
I think we just didn't understand her.
她把我们逼的太紧了
She was smothering us like a pork chop.
但我们意识到可能只是因为她之前没有家人
But we didn't realize it was because she never had a family.
我们认为有个大家庭是理所应当的
We may take it for granted that we have a big family,
但不是每个人都有这种好运气
but not everybody's so lucky.
我们为我们的行为感到十分抱歉
We're really sorry for the way we acted.
希望你们能原谅我们
We hope you can forgive us.
当然可以
Of course I can.
我知道有时候默尔特做的太过火了
I know Myrtle can be a bit much,
但这也正是我爱她的地方
but that's also what I love about her.
她是个急性子
She's a spitfire.
呸
Ugh, bleh.
太矫情了
This is gettin' too mushy for me.
我走了
Scoots out.
西摩  我想我也该道歉
Seymour, I think I owe you an apology too.
不用担心  埃尔伯特
Nah, don't worry about it, Al.
我们不是该去参加生日派对了吗
Don't we have a birthday party to get to?
-没错  -我可以去吗
- You know it! - Can I come too?
你当然得去  西摩
You're gonna have to, Seymour.
因为我的手已经动不了了
I can't move my arms anymore!
生日快乐  奶奶
Happy birthday, Gran Gran!
听见了吗  埃尔伯特
Did you hear that, Al?
他们叫我奶奶了
They called me Gran Gran!
谢谢你们
Oh, thank you, everyone.
谢谢你的蛋糕和派对  奶奶
Thanks for the cake and the party, Gran Gran.
但我们该走了
But we should probably get going.
没问题  我明天会去找你们的
Okay, then, I'll drop by tomorrow.
你可以周日再去吗
Uh... how about Sunday instead?
我买了巡回演出的票
I got us tickets to the RV show tomorrow.
-再见  奶奶  -生日快乐
- Bye, Gran Gran! - Happy birthday!
西摩  别盯着我的蛋糕看
Seymour! Quit eyein' my cake!
你已经把你的那份吃完了
You already had your piece!
我也没办法
I can't help it!
我的左眼根本不受控制
The left one's got a mind of its own.
挤在狭小的房间
<i>Cramped inside this tiny space</i>
■
扫描右侧二维码
关注迪幻微信公众号
获取青春影视资讯趣闻
听来很惨  其实不然
<i>  May sound bad but ain't the case</i>
-喧闹一家亲  -一家亲
<i> - In the Loud house   - Loud house</i>
推搡打闹  追跑躲闪
<i>Duck and dodge and push and shove</i>
是我们对爱的表现  喧闹一家亲
<i>  That's the way we show our love in the Loud house</i>
一家亲
<i>Loud house</i>
脏衣服堆成山
<i>  Laundry piles stacked up high</i>
旧东西代代传
<i>  Hand-me-downs that make me cry</i>
上厕所排长队
<i>  Stand in line to take a pee</i>
任何隐私都玩完
<i>  Never any privacy</i>
十一个孩子闹翻天
<i>  Chaos with 11 kids</i>
生活永远别开生面
<i>  That's the way it always is</i>
喧闹一家亲
<i>  In the Loud house</i>